YWCA of the U.S.A. Records. Record Group 8. Community Associations
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES IV. COMMUNITY ASSOCIATIONS FILES
  - Subseries B. 1988-2002
    - New Jersey
      - Sussex County/Newton
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991 (Box 929)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995 (Box 929)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1917-95 (Box 929)
        - Correspondence, 1969-98 (Box 929)
        - National Association Review Team Report, 1981 (Box 929)
      - Trenton
        - Accreditation requirements
          - 1991-92 (Box 929)
          - 1993-99 (Box 930)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 930)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1998 (Box 930)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 930)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1994-96 (Box 930)
        - Correspondence, 1959-2002, n.d. (Box 930)
        - Program, 1984-98, n.d. (Box 930)
      - Union County, Eastern (Elizabeth)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 930)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 930)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 930)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 930)
        - Board of Directors, 1994-99 (Box 930)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1997 (Box 930)
        - Correspondence, 1994-2002 (Box 930)
        - Program, 1989-99, n.d. (Box 930)
      - Westfield
        - Association Review, 1980 (Box 930)
        - Association Progress Report, 1984 (Box 930)
        - Board of Directors, 1978-80 (Box 930)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1954-81 (Box 930)
        - Correspondence, 1964-85 (Box 930)
    - New Mexico
      - Lea County (Hobbs), 1983-87 (Box 930)
      - Middle Rio Grande/Albuquerque
        - Accreditation requirements, 1987-99 (Box 930)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 930)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1997-98 (Box 930)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 930)
        - Board of Directors, 1995-98 (Box 930)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1988-95 (Box 930)
        - Correspondence, 1984-2001 (Box 930)
        - Program
          - 1993-97 (Box 930)
          - 1998-2000, n.d. (Box 931)
    - New York
      - Adirondack Foothills/Lower Adirondack Foothills/Gloversville
        - Accreditation requirements, 1989-99 (Box 931)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 931)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996 (Box 931)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 931)
        - Board of Directors, 1993, 1996 (Box 931)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995 (Box 931)
        - Correspondence, 1989-2001 (Box 931)
        - Program, 1996-98, n.d. (Box 931)
      - Albany
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-94 (Box 931)
        - Correspondence, 1990-99 (Box 931)
        - Program, 1989-90 (Box 931)
        - Sale of property, 1996 (Box 931)
        - Small claims court case, 1971 (Box 931)
      - Binghamton and Broome County
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 931)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-99 (Box 931)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995, 1997 (Box 931)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 931)
        - Board of Directors, 1992, 1995-98 (Box 931)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995 (Box 931)
        - Correspondence, 1986-2000, n.d. (Box 931)
        - Program, 1993-98, n.d. (Box 931)
      - Brooklyn
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 931)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1996-99 (Box 931)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995, 1997 (Box 931)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 931)
        - Board of Directors, 1991-95 (Box 931)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1993-96 (Box 931)
        - Correspondence, 1989-2001, n.d. (Box 931)
        - Legal: Braithwaite v. YWCA, 1998-2000 (Box 931)
        - Program, 1991-2001, n.d. (Box 931)
      - Cortland
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-98 (Box 931)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 931)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995-1997 (Box 931)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 931)
        - Board of Directors, 1995-97 (Box 932)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996 (Box 932)
        - Correspondence, 1988-98 (Box 932)
        - Program, 1990-2001 (Box 932)
      - Dutchess County (Poughkeepsie) (Box 932)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 932)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 932)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995 (Box 932)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 932)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1994-95 (Box 932)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2000 (Box 932)
        - Program, 1990-98, n.d. (Box 932)
      - Elmira and the Twin Tiers/Chemung County
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 932)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 932)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995-98 (Box 932)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 932)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995 (Box 932)
        - Correspondence, 1989-99 (Box 932)
        - Program, 1990, 1996-98, n.d. (Box 932)
      - Genesee County (Batavia)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 932)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-98 (Box 932)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997-98 (Box 932)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 932)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995 (Box 932)
        - Correspondence, 1987-2001, n.d. (Box 932)
        - Program, 1997, n.d. (Box 932)
      - Jamestown
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 932)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 932)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 932)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 932)
        - Board of Directors, 1995-97 (Box 932)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1984, 1996-97 (Box 932)
        - Correspondence, 1987-99 (Box 932)
        - Program, 1993-98, n.d. (Box 932)
      - Mohawk Valley/Utica
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 932)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-2000 (Box 932)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 932)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 932)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1983-95 (Box 932)
        - Correspondence, 1989-98 (Box 932)
        - Program, 1984-98, n.d. (Box 933)
      - New York, City of
        - Accreditation requirements, 1992-98 (Box 933)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-99 (Box 933)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996 (Box 933)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 933)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1934-96 (Box 933)
        - Correspondence, 1985-2000 (Box 933)
        - New Harlem YWCA
          - General, 1981-90 (Box 933)
          - Constitution/Basic documents, 1982-85 (Box 933)
        - Program, 1970, 1976, 1994-2000, n.d. (Box 933)
      - Niagara/Lockport
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-98 (Box 933)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 933)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996, 1998 (Box 933)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 933)
        - Board of Directors, 1996, 1999-2000 (Box 933)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1915, 1996 (Box 933)
        - Correspondence, 1990-2001, n.d. (Box 933)
        - Program, 1995-2001, n.d. (Box 933)
      - Orange County/Newburgh/Orange Area (New Windsor)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-95 (Box 933)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-95 (Box 933)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995 (Box 933)
        - Board of Directors, 1995, 1997 (Box 933)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1978-ca.1998 (Box 933)
        - Correspondence, 1989-2002 (Box 933)
        - Program, 1992-97, n.d. (Box 933)
      - Rochester and Monroe County
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 933)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 933)
        - Action Audit for Change Process
          - Steering Team Report, 1981 (Box 934)
          - Steering Team Report appendix, 1981 (Box 934)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1996, 1998 (Box 934)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 934)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995, 1998 (Box 934)
        - Correspondence, 1992-99 (Box 934)
        - Personnel Policies, 1983 (Box 934)
        - Program, 1983-2001, n.d. (Box 934)
      - Schenectady
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 934)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 934)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1998 (Box 934)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 934)
        - Board of Directors, 1995, 1997 (Box 934)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1951-96 (Box 934)
        - Correspondence, 1988-99 (Box 934)
        - Legal: Sharpe v. YWCA, 1990 (Box 934)
        - Program, 1980-98, n.d. (Box 934)
      - Syracuse and Onondaga County
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 934)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-99 (Box 934)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1997-98 (Box 934)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 934)
        - Board of Directors, 1989-91 (Box 934)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1987-97 (Box 934)
        - Correspondence, 1988-98 (Box 934)
        - Program, 1979-97, n.d. (Box 934)
      - The Tonawandas
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 934)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 934)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1994, 1997 (Box 934)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 934)
        - Board of Directors, 1997-98 (Box 934)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1913-97 (Box 934)
        - Correspondence, 1990-2000 (Box 934)
        - Program, 1989-96, n.d. (Box 934)
      - Troy-Cohoes
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-98 (Box 934)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 934)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1997 (Box 934)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 934)
        - Board of Directors, 1997-98 (Box 935)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1965-97 (Box 935)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2000 (Box 935)
        - Program, 1957-2002, n.d. (Box 935)
      - Ulster County (Kingston)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-98 (Box 935)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 935)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996 (Box 935)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 935)
        - Board of Directors, 1995 (Box 935)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1980, 1996 (Box 935)
        - Correspondence, 1990-2001 (Box 935)
        - Program, 1996-98, n.d. (Box 935)
      - Watertown
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-92 (Box 935)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991 (Box 935)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1916-93 (Box 935)
        - Correspondence, 1986-96, n.d. (Box 935)
      - Western New York/Buffalo and Erie County (Buffalo)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 935)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1990-99 (Box 935)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 935)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 935)
        - Board of Directors, 1988-98 (Box 935)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996 (Box 935)
        - Correspondence, 1993-99 (Box 935)
        - Program, 1993-2001, n.d. (Box 935)
      - Westfield
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 935)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 935)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 935)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 935)
        - Board of Directors, 1995-98 (Box 935)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1989, 1995 (Box 935)
        - Correspondence, 1987-2000, n.d. (Box 935)
        - Program, 1994-98, n.d. (Box 935)
      - White Plains and [Central] Westchester
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 936)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 936)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 936)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 936)
        - Board of Directors, 1995-98 (Box 936)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1970-95 (Box 936)
        - Correspondence, 1990-2002 (Box 936)
        - Program, 1972-2000, n.d. (Box 936)
      - Yonkers
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 936)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1992-97 (Box 936)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995 (Box 936)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 936)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1895, 1995-99 (Box 936)
        - Correspondence, 1989-2002, n.d. (Box 936)
        - Program, 1991-2000, n.d. (Box 936)
    - North Carolina
      - Asheville
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 936)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 936)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995 (Box 936)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 936)
        - Board of Directors, 1989-91 (Box 936)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1907-2000 (Box 936)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2001 (Box 936)
        - Program, 1987 (Box 936)
      - Central Carolinas/Charlotte
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-97 (Box 936)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1992-97 (Box 936)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1997 (Box 936)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 936)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, ca. 1991-96 (Box 936)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2001 (Box 936)
        - Pool Site Inspection Report, 1991 (Box 937)
        - Program, 1992-97 (Box 937)
      - Greensboro
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 937)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 937)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 937)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 937)
        - Board of Directors, 1990-99 (Box 937)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995-97 (Box 937)
        - Correspondence, 1990-2000 (Box 937)
        - Program, 1988-97, n.d. (Box 937)
      - High Point/Adams Memorial YWCA
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 937)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 937)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1994, 1995, 1997 (Box 937)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 937)
        - Board of Directors, 1990, 1995 (Box 937)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1920, 1996-99 (Box 937)
        - Correspondence, 1977-2000 (Box 937)
        - Program, 1989-97, n.d. (Box 937)
      - Rocky Mount
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-98 (Box 937)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 937)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1998 (Box 937)
        - Board of Directors, 1990-97 (Box 937)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1920-97 (Box 937)
        - Correspondence, 1989-2001 (Box 937)
        - Program, 1990-92, n.d. (Box 937)
      - Wake County/Raleigh
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 937)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 937)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995 (Box 937)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 937)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995-96 (Box 937)
        - Correspondence, 1980-2000 (Box 937)
        - Program, 1989-93 (Box 937)
      - Wilmington
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 937)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 938)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995, 1997 (Box 938)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 938)
        - Board of Directors, 1990 (Box 938)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995 (Box 938)
        - Correspondence, 1985-98 (Box 938)
        - Program, 1986-98, n.d. (Box 938)
      - Winston-Salem and Forsyth County/Winston-Salem
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 938)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 938)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1994, 1996 (Box 938)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 938)
        - Board of Directors, 1986-87, 1996 (Box 938)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1914-96 (Box 938)
        - Correspondence, 1967, 1990-99, n.d. (Box 938)
        - Pool Site Inspection Report, 1991 (Box 938)
        - Program, 1983-98, n.d. (Box 938)
    - North Dakota
      - Fargo-Moorhead
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 938)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 938)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1994-97 (Box 938)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 938)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1921-96, n.d. (Box 938)
        - Correspondence, 1963, 1978, 1987-99, n.d. (Box 938)
        - Program, 1990-98, n.d. (Box 938)
      - Minot
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 938)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1992-99 (Box 938)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1993, 1995, 1997 (Box 938)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 938)
        - Board of Directors, 1990-92 (Box 938)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1914-96 (Box 938)
        - Correspondence, 1975-2000 (Box 938)
        - Program, n.d. (Box 938)
    - Ohio
      - Alliance
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 938)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 938)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 938)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 938)
        - Board of Directors, 1995, 1997-98 (Box 938)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995 (Box 938)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2000, n.d. (Box 938)
        - Program, 1991-97, n.d. (Box 939)
      - Canton
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 939)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 939)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996-97 (Box 939)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 939)
        - Board of Trustees, 1996-2000 (Box 939)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1993 (Box 939)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2001, n.d. (Box 939)
        - Program, 1989-2000, n.d. (Box 939)
      - Cincinnati
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 939)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-97 (Box 939)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 939)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 939)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996 (Box 939)
        - Correspondence, 1989-2001 (Box 939)
        - Program, 1991-99, n.d. (Box 939)
      - Cleveland
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 939)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 939)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996, 1998 (Box 939)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 939)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996 (Box 939)
        - Correspondence, 1988-99 (Box 939)
        - National Technical Assistance Team visit, 1987 (Box 939)
        - Program, 1988-2001, n.d. (Box 939)
      - Columbus
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 939)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential
          - 1990-93 (Box 939)
          - 1994-99 (Box 940)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995 (Box 940)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 940)
        - Board of Trustees, 1992-96 (Box 940)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1972, 1996 (Box 940)
        - Correspondence, 1986-2000, n.d. (Box 940)
        - Program, 1995-99, n.d. (Box 940)
      - Coshocton County
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 940)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1992-99 (Box 940)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995-96 (Box 940)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 940)
        - Board of Directors, 1992, 1995, 1997-98 (Box 940)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1995 (Box 940)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2001 (Box 940)
        - Program, 1990-2001, n.d. (Box 940)
      - Dayton
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-98 (Box 940)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1994-97 (Box 940)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1998 (Box 940)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 940)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1997-98 (Box 940)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2001 (Box 940)
        - Program, 1970-99, n.d. (Box 940)
      - Elyria (see also Lorain)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-97 (Box 940)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-95 (Box 940)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995 (Box 940)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 940)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996 (Box 940)
        - Correspondence, 1989-2000, n.d. (Box 940)
        - Program, 1995-97, n.d. (Box 940)
      - Hamilton
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 940)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 940)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1998 (Box 940)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 940)
        - Board of Directors, 1991, 1995 (Box 940)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1902, 1996 (Box 940)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2001, n.d. (Box 940)
        - Program, 1996-98, n.d. (Box 940)
      - Licking County (Newark)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-97 (Box 940)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-95 (Box 940)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996 (Box 940)
        - Board of Directors, 1986, 1993-96 (Box 940)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996 (Box 940)
        - Correspondence, 1978-2001 (Box 940)
        - Program, 1985-90, n.d. (Box 940)
      - Lima
        - Accreditation requirements
          - 1990-92 (Box 940)
          - 1993-99 (Box 941)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 941)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996-97 (Box 941)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 941)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1996-97 (Box 941)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2001 (Box 941)
        - Program, 1977, n.d. (Box 941)
      - Lorain (see also Elyria)
        - Accreditation requirements, 1990-99 (Box 941)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-98 (Box 941)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1995, 1997 (Box 941)
        - Board of Directors, 1991-95 (Box 941)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1994, 1995 (Box 941)
        - Correspondence, 1988-2002, n.d. (Box 941)
        - Legal: Lorain National Bank v. YWCA of Lorain, 2000-02 (Box 941)
        - Program, 1993-96, n.d. (Box 941)
      - Mansfield
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-96 (Box 941)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-96 (Box 941)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1990, 1995 (Box 941)
        - Board of Directors, 1990-95 (Box 941)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1974-95 (Box 941)
        - Correspondence, 1988-99, n.d. (Box 941)
        - Program, 1957-93, n.d. (Box 941)
      - Massillon [becomes Western Stark County?]
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 941)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 941)
        - Affiliation requirements, 1996, 1998 (Box 941)
        - Annual Statistical Report Form, 2000 (Box 941)
        - Constitution/Basic documents, 1982-96 (Box 941)
        - Correspondence, 1991-2001 (Box 941)
        - Program, 1997-98, n.d. (Box 941)
      - Medina County
        - Accreditation requirements, 1991-99 (Box 941)
        - Accreditation: personnel confidential, 1991-99 (Box 941)